<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MIT Movies</string>
    <string name="toy_stroy_3">The toys are mistakenly delivered to a day care center instead of the attic right before Andy leaves for college,
        and its up to Woody to convince the other toys that they werent abandoned and to return home</string>
    <string name="toy_stroy">A cowboy doll is profoundly threatened and jealous when a new spaceman figure supplants him as top toy ina boys room.</string>
    <string name="nightmare">Jack Skellington king of Halloween Town, discovers Christmas Town, but his attempts to bring Christmas to his home causes confusion.</string>
    <string name="dragon">A hapless young Viking who aspires to hunt dragons becomes the unlikely friend of a young dragon himself, and learns there may be more to the creatures than he assumed.</string>
    <string name="lionking">Lion prince Simba and his father are targeted by his bitter uncle, who wants to ascend the throne himself.</string>
    <string name="lilo">A young and parent less girl adopts a dog from the local pound, completely unaware that its supposedly a dangerous scientific experiment thats taken refuge on Earth and is now hiding from its creator and those who see it as a menace.</string>
    <string name="rat">A rat who can cook makes an unusual alliance with a young kitchen worker at a famous Paris restaurant.</string>
    <string name="caroline">An adventurous 11-year-old girl finds another world that is a strangely idealized version of her frustrating home, but it has sinister secrets.</string>
    <string name="up">An adventurous 11-year-old girl finds another world that is a strangely idealized version of her frustrating home, but it has sinister secrets.</string>
    <string name="wall">In the distant future, a small waste-collecting robot inadvertently embarks on a space journey that will ultimately decide the fate of mankind.</string>
    <string name="darkknight">When the menace known as the Joker wreaks havoc and chaos on the people of Gotham, Batman must accept one of the greatest psychological and physical tests of his ability to fight injustice.</string>
    <string name="thelegend">Eight years after the Jokers reign of anarchy, Batman, with the help of the enigmatic Catwoman, is forced from his exile to save Gotham City from the brutal guerrilla terrorist Bane.</string>
    <string name="thegardian">A group of intergalactic criminals must pull together to stop a fanatical warrior with plans to purge the universe.</string>
    <string name="ironman">A group of intergalactic criminals must pull together to stop a fanatical warrior with plans to purge the universe.</string>
    <string name="captain">As Steve Rogers struggles to embrace his role in the modern world, he teams up with a fellow Avenger and S.H.I.E.L.D agent, Black Widow, to battle a new threat from history: an assassin known as the Winter Soldier.</string>
    <string name="spideerman">A strange black entity from another world bonds with Peter Parker and causes inner turmoil as he contends with new villains, temptations, and revenge.</string>
    <string name="wolverine">Wolverine comes to Japan to meet an old friend whose life he saved years ago, and gets embroiled in a conspiracy involving yakuza and mutants.</string>
    <string name="batman">After training with his mentor, Batman begins his fight to free crime-ridden Gotham City from corruption..</string>
    <string name="manofsteel">An alien child is evacuated from his dying world and sent to Earth to live among humans. His peace is threatened, when other survivors of his home planet invade Earth..</string>
    <string name="thor">When the Dark Elves attempt to plunge the universe into darkness, Thor must embark on a perilous and personal journey that will reunite him with doctor Jane Foster.</string>



</resources>